https://lattanzilaw.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
PRIVACY PROTECTION POLICY OF GREGORY T. LATTANZI, LLCTO COMPLY WITH CONNECTICUT GENERAL STATUTES SECTION 42-471IT IS THE POLICY OF GREGORY T. LATTANZI, LLC TO PROTECT THE PRIVACY OF OUR CLIENTS. WE DO NOT DISCLOSE ANY NON-PUBLIC PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO ANYONE FOR ANY PURPOSE THAT IS NOT SPECIFICALLY PERMITTED BY LAW.
We make reasonable efforts to restrict access to non-public personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you. We make reasonable efforts to train those employees to protect the privacy of our clients. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal and state law to guard your non-public personal information.
It is the policy of this law firm to:
Safeguarding any data, computer files and documents containing your personal information from any
misuse by third parties; and
Destroying, erasing or making unreadable any data, computer files and documents containing your
personal information prior to disposal; and
Protect the confidentiality of Social Security numbers and non-public personal information; and
Prohibit the unlawful disclosure of Social Security numbers and non-public personal information; and
Limit access to Social Security numbers and non-public personal Information.
943 Grand Ave, New Haven, CT 06511
Monroe Building 87 Whitfield St, 2nd Floor, Guilford, CT 06437
929 Kings Hwy E, 1st Floor, Fairfield, CT 06825
(203) 772-3000
(203) 772-3600
realestate@lattanzilaw.com
Mon - Thu: 8:30 - 5:00PM | Fri: 8:30 - 4:00PM - Shorline & Fairfield Offices Are By Appointment Only.
© 2019, Law Offices Of Gregory T. Lattanzi, LLC. All Rights Reserved.
